(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
パレ、パレ、パレ 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade. Shine on.
呼び合う声を合図に
With the voices calling out to each other as a signal.
パレ、パレ、パレ 探しに行く
Parade, parade, parade. I'm going to search.
スタートは何度だって
No matter how many times we start.
Our Bright Parade
作詞・作曲：堀江晶太
Lyrics & Composition: Shota Horie
ただ独り言 綴った
I just wrote down my soliloquy.
ただ始めたくて 走った
I just wanted to start, so I ran.
遠く暗がりに灯った
Lit up in the distant darkness.
それは眩しすぎた名前
That name was too dazzling.
それは優しすぎる思い出
Those memories are too kind.
もっと近づけて手を伸ばした
I reached out my hand to get closer.
想いだけ紡ぎ合った
We only spun our feelings together.
ほら 今 迷い子は僕らになった
Look, now we've become lost children.
パレ、パレ、パレ 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade. Shine on.
悔しさも愛しさも連れておいで
Bring your frustrations and your affection.
馳せ、ゆめ、晴れ 飛び出せるさ
Racing, dreaming, clearing. We can fly out.
ささやかな祈りは光
A small prayer is a light.
終わりのない日差し
Endless sunlight.
君を見つけたこと 胸を張れるよ
I can be proud that I found you.
ここから、これから
From here, from now on.
Our Bright Parade, Parade
まだ頼りない予感も
Even the still unreliable premonition.
歌おう 恥ずかしくなんてないよ
Let's sing, there's nothing to be ashamed of.
誰も解けない魔法
Magic that no one can break.
いつかまた会えるおまじない
A spell so we can meet again someday.
あの日のゼロに始まった
It started from zero on that day.
ストーリー 伝えきれない言の葉
Story, words that can't be fully conveyed.
数えるような想いじゃないさ
It's not the kind of feeling you can count.
ほら 今 僕らをひとつと呼ぼう
Look, now let's call us one.
パレ、パレ、パレ 美しいんだよ
Parade, parade, parade. It's beautiful.
許しあえる刹那 夜はきらめく
The moment we can forgive each other, the night sparkles.
晴れ、晴れ、晴れ まなざし空
Clear, clear, clear, gazing at the sky.
ふさわしい旅路とは 君と歩くことさ
A fitting journey is walking with you.
君と歩くことなんだ
It's about walking with you.
「ただいま」を聞けば 「おかえり」って叫ぶよ
If I hear 'I'm home,' I'll shout 'Welcome back.'
当たり前じゃないから
Because it's not something to be taken for granted.
パレ、パレ、パレ 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade. Shine on.
暗がりを満たすのは 君だ、僕だ
It's you and me who fill the darkness.
パレ、パレ、パレ
Parade, parade, parade.
風、夢、羽根、輝くんだよ
Wind, dreams, feathers, they're shining!
悔しさも愛おしさも
Both frustration and affection
連れておいで
Bring them along
風、夢、羽根、飛び立つのさ
Wind, dreams, feathers, we're taking flight!
さあさあ舞い踊れ光、終わりなき予兆
Now, now, dance in the light, an endless omen
君と飛び込んでいく、素敵なスタートさ
Diving in with you, it's a wonderful start!
ここから、これから、Our Bright Parade!
From here, from now on, Our Bright Parade!
無敵の笑顔で荒らすメディア
The media is disrupted by your invincible smile
知りたいその秘密ミステリアス
Everyone wants to know your secrets, so mysterious
抜けてるとこさえ彼女のエリア
Even your clumsy side is part of your domain
完璧で嘘つきな君は
You are perfect and a liar
天才的なアイドル様
A genius idol
アイドル
作詞・作曲：Ayase
Idol
Lyrics/Composition: Ayase
今日何食べた？好きな本は？
What did you eat today? What's your favorite book?
遊びに行くならどこに行くの？
If you were to go out, where would you go?
何も食べてない、それは内緒
I haven't eaten anything, that's a secret
何を聞かれてものらりくらり
No matter what I'm asked, I dodge the questions
淡々と、だけど燦々と
Calmly, yet brilliantly
見えそうで見えない秘密は蜜の味
Secrets that are almost visible yet hidden taste like honey
あれもないないない、これもないないない
Not that, not this, nothing at all
好きなタイプは？相手は？さあ答えて
What's your type? Who's the lucky one? Come on, answer me!
「誰かを好きになることなんて私分からなくてさ」
"I don't really understand what it means to fall in love with someone."
嘘か本当か知り得ない、そんな言葉にまた一人堕ちる
Not knowing if it's a lie or the truth, another person falls for those words
また好きにさせる
Making them fall in love again
誰もが目を奪われていく
Everyone is captivated by you
君は完璧で究極のアイドル
You are the perfect and ultimate idol
金輪際現れない、一番星の生まれ変わり
A once-in-a-lifetime occurrence, the reincarnation of the first star
その笑顔で愛してるで、誰も彼も虜にしていく
With that smile and "I love you," you captivate everyone
その瞳がその言葉が、嘘でもそれは完全なアイ
Even if your eyes and those words are lies, it's a perfect love
はいはいあの子は特別です
Yeah, yeah, that girl is special
我々はハナからおまけです
We were just extras from the start
お星様の引き立て役Bです
Just a supporting cast B to make the star shine
全てがあの子のお陰なわけない
Not everything is thanks to her
洒落臭い、妬み嫉妬なんてないわけがない
How annoying, there's no way we don't feel envy or jealousy
これはネタじゃないからこそ許せない
This isn't a joke, which makes it unforgivable
完璧じゃない君じゃ許せない
I can't forgive you if you're not perfect
自分を許せない
I can't forgive myself
誰よりも強い君以外は認めない
I won't acknowledge anyone but you, who is stronger than anyone
誰もが信じ崇めてる
Everyone believes in and worships you
まさに最強で無敵のアイドル
Truly the strongest and invincible idol
弱点なんて見当たらない、一番星を宿している
No weaknesses to be found, carrying the first star within you
弱いとこなんて見せちゃダメダメ
Don't you dare show any weaknesses
知りたくないとこは見せずに
Without showing the parts people don't want to see
唯一無二じゃなくちゃイヤイヤ、それこそ本物のアイ
You must be one of a kind, that's what true love is
得意の笑顔で沸かすメディア
Inciting the media with your signature smile
隠しきるこの秘密だけは
Keeping only this secret hidden
愛してるって嘘で積むキャリア
Building a career on "I love you" lies
これこそ私なりの愛だ
This is my own way of showing love
流れる汗も綺麗なアクア
Even the trickling sweat is beautiful aqua
ルビーを隠したこの瞼
These eyelids that hide the rubies
歌い踊り舞う私はマリア
Singing and dancing, I am Mary
そう、嘘はとびきりの愛だ
Yes, lies are the ultimate form of love
誰かに愛されたことも、誰かのこと愛したこともない
Never been loved by anyone, nor have I ever loved anyone
そんな私の嘘がいつか、本当になること
That lie of mine will one day become the truth
信じてる
I believe
いつかきっと全部手に入れる
One day I'll surely have it all
私はそう欲張りなアイドル
I'm such a greedy idol
等身大でみんなのこと、ちゃんと愛したいから
Because I want to love everyone for who I really am
今日も嘘をつくの
I'll keep lying today
この言葉がいつか本当になる日を願って
Hoping that these words will one day become the truth
それでもまだ君と君にだけは言えずにいたけど
Even so, there's still something I couldn't say to you and only you
ああ、やっと言えた、これは絶対嘘じゃない
Ah, I finally said it, and this is definitely not a lie
愛してる
I love you
はい！ということで始まりました！皆さんこんらみー！
All right! And so it begins! Hello everyone, Kon-Lamy!
ホロライブ5期生の、高潔、肝臓、雪花ラミィです！
I'm the noble liver of Hololive's 5th generation, Yukihana Lamy!
ラミィちゃんしか！勝たん！
Lamy-chan is the best!
うーみー！
U-mi-!
愛してるのはー、ラミィちゃーん！
The one I love is... Lamy-chan!
ということで、ありがとうみんなー！
And with that, thank you everyone!
えー、今回のハッシュタグはこちら！
Now, today's hashtag is this!
「#雪花ラミィ3周年ライブ」となっております。
It's "#YukihanaLamy3rdAnniversaryLive."
そして、この後ろのモニターに映っている、「Lamy Love Fest」！
And displayed on the monitor behind me is "Lamy Love Fest"!
こちらね、この名前の通り、
As the name suggests,
今日のライブはラミィの「大好き」をたくさん詰め込んだお祭りとなっています！
today's live is a festival packed with all of Lamy's favorite things!
これからゲストパートに入るわけなんですけれども、
We're about to move on to the guest part,
ラミィの大好きなホロメンと
and with my favorite Hololive members,
ラミィがずっと歌いたかった、あんな曲やこんな曲を一緒に踊って歌っていきたいと思います！
I'll be singing and dancing to all the songs I've always wanted to perform!
そして今日はね、みんな！
And today, everyone,
待ちに待ったあの子が登場です！雪民さーん！
that character you've all been waiting for is here! Yukimin!
わー！かわいい！みんな見て見て！
Wow! So cute! Everyone, look, look!
ついに雪花ラミィ3周年記念にして、
Finally, for my 3rd anniversary,
雪民さんが3Dで登場しました！みんな見て！ほら！
Yukimin has appeared in 3D! Look, everyone!
あー、かわいい！かわいいー！
Ah, so cute! So cute!
よしよし。いい子、いい子。
There, there. Good boy.
あら？寝ちゃった。ほらほら。
Oh? He fell asleep. Come on.
雪民さん寝ちゃったのー？
Did you fall asleep, Yukimin?
いいの？寝ちゃっても。
Is it okay to sleep right now?
今からライブ見るんじゃないの？一緒に応援してくれるんじゃないの？えー、起きて！
Aren't you going to watch the live? Aren't you going to cheer? Hey, wake up!
起きて起きて起きて起きて起きてー！
Wake up, wake up, wake up, wake up, wake up!
雪民さん起きてーーー！
Yukimin, wake up!
あ、起きた。起きてよかった、安心したよ。
Oh, he's awake. I'm so relieved.
じゃあね、雪民さんも起きたところで、今回ね、
Now that Yukimin is awake, for this event,
みんな一曲目で気づいたと思うけれど、
I think you all noticed during the first song,
これ、見てください！ドドン！
but please look at this! Ta-da!
雪花ラミィ、アイドルステージができましたー！イエーイ！
Yukihana Lamy's idol stage is complete! Yay!
このね、雪花ラミィのステージもこだわりがいっぱい詰まっているんですよ。
This Yukihana Lamy stage is also filled with special touches.
ということで、ちょっとね、紹介していきたいと思いますけれども、
So, I'd like to show them to you.
まず、見てください！こだわりのバルーンアート。え、つみれの姿となっております。
First, look at this! Custom balloon art in the shape of Tsumire.
いや、かわいいでしょ、これ。
Isn't it just adorable?
そして、こっちには、ジャン！
And over here, ta-da!
だいふくがペンライト振ってくれています！
Daifuku is waving a penlight for me!
かわいい！だいふくも大きくなったなー。
So cute! Daifuku has really grown up too.
そして、こっちには、
And then, over here...
雪民さんが、大きいのと中くらいのと小さいのの
The three Yukimin brothers—big, medium, and small—
三兄弟がペンライト振って応援してくれてます！
are waving their penlights to cheer me on!
そして、みんなほら！
And look at this, everyone!
ちょっと見えるかな？これこれこれこれ！これもつみれの形を、あ、今ついてないけど、
Can you see? This one here! It's in the shape of Tsumire—oh, it's off right now, but—
つみれのね、形をモニターにしていただきました！
I had them make a monitor in the shape of Tsumire!
雪民さん、ほら！あ、映ってるよ、
Look, Yukimin! Oh, you're on screen!
雪民さん映ってるよ！えーい！
You're on the monitor! Yay!
というね、もうこのこだわりのステージ！
This is the stage I've put so much thought into!
いや、もう本当にラミィ3周年にして、こんなに、こんなに色んなことがね、
Seriously, for my 3rd anniversary, so many things...
一気に起きてしまったので、ラミィもちょっとついていけてないところはありますけれども、
have happened all at once that even I'm having trouble keeping up!
この後は、ついにゲストパート！
And next is finally the guest part!
そして最後は、みんなも楽しみにしているあれが来るかもしれません。
And at the very end, that thing you're all waiting for might just happen.
ということでね、みんな、行きますか？
So, everyone, are you ready to go?
ゲストパート、レッツ！
To the guest part! Let's...
の前に、
Wait, before that!
らーみゅーん、まー！えい！
Lamyuun-ma! *pose*
行ってきます！
Here I go!
もぐもぐYUMMY！もぐもぐYUMMY！もぐもぐ... もぐもぐ...
Mogu mogu yummy! Mogu mogu yummy! Mogu mogu... Mogu mogu...
森羅万象のアクセンとも、
Even the accents of all creation,
マヨネーズかけた
doused in mayonnaise
だらだらいたい おいしくなる
I want to be lazy, and then it becomes delicious.
君が泣いても お腹は空くよ
Even if you cry, I still get hungry.
消化できなかった ごめんごめん
I couldn't digest it, sorry, sorry.
酸いも甘いも 勝手に食べて
Eating the sours and sweets as I please.
ご迷惑おかけしています
I'm causing a bit of trouble.
パクチーおきて 変な味ジュース
Cilantro wakeup, strange-tasting juice.
心を無にして 飲み込みます
Emptying my mind and swallowing it down.
ああ 混沌情報過多のレストランで
Ah, in a restaurant overflowing with chaotic information.
嘘っぱちのメニューに お茶こぼして
Spilling tea on the fake menu.
君ともぐもぐ もぐもぐ もぐもぐ
Munching away with you, munch, munch.
銃撃戦の真ん中で もぐもぐ
Munching away in the middle of a gunfight.
（うぎゃ～）
(Ugyaaa~)
魑魅魍魎 ハラペコの群れ
A crowd of hungry monsters.
満腹になる未来を 願っているよ
I'm wishing for a future where we're full.
もぐもぐ もぐもぐ もぐもぐ
Munch munch, munch munch, munch munch.
世界が終わる前に
Before the world ends.
もぐもぐ やみい マジ神
Munch munch, yummy, seriously godlike.
やむやむ ありのまんま
Yum yum, just as I am.
もぐもぐ やみい マジ神
Munch munch, yummy, seriously godlike.
この世を味わうんだ うまうま
Tasting this world, delicious.
理論武装のミルフィーユサンド
A mille-feuille sandwich of theoretical defenses.
匿名希望のオーロラソース
Aurora sauce for an anonymous requester.
おざっぱな味付けを 目にみてよ
Take a look at the rough seasoning.
美味しくなったら OK OK
If it becomes delicious, it's OK OK.
良いモン 悪いモン いっぱい食べて
Eating lots of good things and bad things.
汚れた口元 拭います
Wiping my messy mouth.
おにぎり ピザ ケーキ 豪華なフルコース
Rice balls, pizza, cake—a luxurious full course.
罠を疑い 気をつけます
Suspecting traps, I'll be careful.
ああ 妄想流言飛語のバイキングで
Ah, at a buffet of delusions and rumors.
毒入りと絶品料理 選り分けて
Sorting out the poisoned ones from the masterpieces.
君ともぐもぐ もぐもぐ もぐもぐ
Munching away with you, munch, munch.
デスゲームの教室で もぐもぐ
Munching away in a death game classroom.
魑魅魍魎 ハラペコの群れ
A crowd of hungry monsters.
仲の良い君と 生き残れたらいいな
I hope I can survive with you, my good friend.
もぐもぐ もぐもぐ もぐもぐ
Munch munch, munch munch, munch munch.
数年後もこの場所で
Even years later, in this same place.
もぐもぐ やみい マジ神
Munch munch, yummy, seriously godlike.
今夜の晩ごはんは もぐもぐ
Tonight's dinner is... munch munch.
やみい マジ神
Yummy, seriously godlike.
次はお前の番だ もぐもぐ
Next is your turn, munch munch.
やみい マジ神
Yummy, seriously godlike.
やむやむ ありのまんま
Yum yum, just as I am.
もぐもぐ やみい マジ神
Munch munch, yummy, seriously godlike.
この世を味わうんだ うまうま
Tasting this world, delicious.
ラミィ、3周年おめでとう！
Lamy, happy 3rd anniversary!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
ありがとうー！
二人目のゲストは、かなたんだー！
The second guest is Kanatan!
うおー！ ほりれぱの絆、見せるぞ！
Whoo! I'll show you the bond of Holirepa!
ラミィ、3周年おめでとう！
Lamy, happy 3rd anniversary!
この曲は早くて高くてなかなか覚えられなかった曲ですが、がんばれラミィ！ 行けー！
This song is fast and high-pitched, so I had a hard time learning it, but do your best, Lamy! Let's go!
特者生存ワンダラダー！！
Tokusha Seizon Wonder-la-der!!
ナヌ！？
What!?
ヒッ！
Eek!
オヤ？
Oh?
マシッ
Mash...
ズコニモサイテ 本質開成
Blooming even in failures, a return to nature.
サワー ボロ キュム マキ 手にする全部 It's my good Luckで
Sour, rag, cum, wrap—everything I grab is part of my good luck.
適度にがんばろっか
Let's do our best in moderation.
そんなんだっていいけどさ
Though that's fine too.
必死にがんばろっか
Let's give it our all.
それが僕の信条だ
That's my creed.
かさつきじゃねーんだわ
I'm not feeling dry at all.
そんでビンボーじゃねーんだわ
And I'm not poor either.
塩梅バッチリいけてる！ 決まってる！
Everything's perfectly seasoned! It's settled!
Are you?
かなたちゃーん！
Kanata-chan!
どどん！ 前進上等！ ちゃんと歓迎して！
Boom! Full speed ahead! Welcome me properly!
(Wonder-la-der-la)
高まれ！ 海空創造 ちゃんと賞賛して！
Soar high! Creation of sea and sky, praise me properly!
(Wonder-la-der-la)
興奮しよう
Let's get excited.
僕が言うんだもん
Because I'm saying so.
本当にするんだもん
Because I really will.
現実超えろ未来
Surpass reality, the future.
あー！ 弱点も平気
Ah! Weaknesses are no problem.
スイッチでランチャー！
Launch with a switch!
(Wonder-la-der-la)
すなわち特者生存ワンダランDAY
In other words, a special survivor wonder-run day.
(Wonder-la-der-la)
楽しもう
Let's have fun.
面白がれること探したまえ Over?
Find something you can enjoy. Over?
返事聞かせてくれ！
Let me hear your answer!
右左なんかじゃない
It's not about right or left.
決めつけて一直線
Deciding and heading straight ahead.
つまり企んだら発射オーライだ
Basically, once planned, it's all systems go.
ワクワクすんぜ！
I'm getting excited!
しゃー！！
Yeah!!
見て！推し引きいた！アイドル作戦楽しい！
Look! I pulled my fave! Being an idol is fun!
でもガッキーの結婚は立ち直ってませーん！
But I still haven't gotten over Gakky's marriage!
ガチャが出るまで回せば100％ピックアップ！ハハハ！天井で！
If you roll until you get it, it's 100% pick-up! Hahaha! At pity!
なんだよ、そんなこと言っちゃダメだ、おバカ！
What was that? You shouldn't say things like that, you dummy!
うわ〜すごい！ありがちぉ！
Whoa~ amazing! Thank you!
(It's my thousand go my way)
虎視眈々でいいんだもん だって
It's fine to wait for the chance, because...
意気ガンガンでいいんだもん
it's fine to be full of spirit.
全方位に勝算アンテナ張っていなくっちゃ
I have to keep my winning antenna up in all directions.
いつでも 心はちゃんと純粋で
My heart is always truly pure...
(wonder-la-der-la)
いたいな 好奇心は絶えず熱心で
and I want to stay that way, with constant curiosity.
(wonder-la-der-la)
いたいなって 言い聞かせるんだ
I tell myself I want to stay that way.
調子に乗ったら すぐ飽きられちゃうから
Because if I get carried away, people will get tired of me soon.
あー！タイトなロープも どんとこいでっせ
Ah! Even a tight rope, bring it on!
(wonder-la-der-la)
すなわち 特者生存ワンダラダーDAY
In other words, a survivors' Wonder-la-der DAY.
(wonder-la-der-la)
かみつけ “努力とは最後まで諦めないこと”
Snap at it! "Effort means not giving up until the end."
メモっておいて！
Make a note of that!
ホントはbaby 自信なんかないよ
Actually, baby, I have no confidence.
ホントはbaby 不安ばっかで泣きそう
Actually, baby, I'm just anxious and about to cry.
でもねbaby くじけないって決めたの
But you know, baby, I decided not to give up.
だからbaby 挑戦したいよ
So, baby, I want to challenge myself.
未開の地 未限のフィールドで
In the unexplored territory, on an infinite field.
ギター！
Guitar!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
前進上等！ちゃんと歓迎して
Moving forward is best! Welcome it properly.
(wonder-la-der-la)
高まれ
Rise up.
海創創造 ちゃんと共鳴して
Open the creation, resonate properly.
(wonder-la-der-la)
興奮しよう
Let's get excited.
ボクが言うんだもん
Because I'm saying it.
本当にするんだもん
Because I'll make it real.
現実超える未来
The future that exceeds reality.
あー！
Ah!
弱点も平気 スイッチでランチャー
Even weaknesses are fine, switch on the launcher.
(wonder-la-der-la)
すなわち 特者生存ワンダラダーDAY
In other words, a survivors' Wonder-la-der DAY.
(wonder-la-der-la)
楽しもう
Let's have fun.
面白がれること 探し放題でっせ
Looking for things to enjoy as much as you like!
無限のフィールドで
On an infinite field.
パンニングしなくてもいい
No need for panning.
ど真ん中一直線
Straight down the middle.
つまりこれが僕の答えなんだ
In short, this is my answer.
胸を張れ
Stand tall.
今を生きるその意味を
The meaning of living in the now.
明くる日もあくるくる日も 確かめ進め！
Every day and the next, make sure and move forward!
うぉー！
Woah!
これぞ最強ワンダラダー！
This is the strongest Wonder-la-der!
ゴリラバスかなたー！
Gorilla Bus Kanata!
サンキュー！
Thank you!
ワン ツー で参拝！みこみこみこ！
One, two, and pray! Mikomikomiko!
(いぇーい！)
(Yay!)
ついに来たよお待たせ！
Finally here, sorry for the wait!
待ちに待った うへへへ
Waited and waited, uhehehe.
電脳世界からやってきた
I came from the cyber world.
ウザカワ系バーチャルみこ
The annoying-cute virtual Miko.
相手は私はそうエリート
The opponent is me, the elite.
(エリート？)
(Elite?)
何て言ったってエリート
No matter what you say, an elite.
(えへへ)
(Ehehe)
エリート巫女？
Elite Miko?
(みこ？)
(Miko?)
エリートアイドル？
Elite idol?
(アイドル？)
(Idol?)
どっちも両方に決まってるじゃん
Of course it's both.
いじわるも泣き虫も
Both the meanies and the crybabies...
カミサマも崇めたら
and even the gods, if you worship them...
みこパワーで幸せ分けて
I'll share happiness with Miko Power.
あげてもいいんだよ？
I could even give some to you, you know?
みこちゃんはー？
Miko-chan is...?
エリートです！
An elite!
みこみこみこで ほにゃほにゃうにゃにゃ
Mikomikomiko, hon-nyanya un-nyanya.
さくら くら くら さくらみこ
Sakura, dizzy, dizzy, Sakura Miko.
(みこ！みこ！)
(Miko! Miko!)
みこみこみこで むにゃむにゃぐーぐー
Mikomikomiko, munya-munya goo-goo.
(ぐー！)
(Goo!)
明日から本気だす！
I'll get serious tomorrow!
(エリートですから！)
(Because I'm an elite!)
みこみこみこで ほにゃほにゃうにゃにゃ
Mikomikomiko, hon-nyanya un-nyanya.
(エリート！)
(Elite!)
金時は ほにゃにゃにゃにゃ…
Kintoki is hon-nyanya-nyanya...
たぶん！
Maybe!
幸せのてこ ポンポコリンリンリン
The lever of happiness, ponpoko-rin-rin-rin.
みんな笑顔になあれ！
Everyone, smile!
ワン ツー で参拝！みこみこみこ！
One, two, and pray! Mikomikomiko!
(いぇーい！)
(Yay!)
ちょっとのけぞけ大体
Approximately leaning back a bit.
マイペースだけど許してね
It's at my own pace, but please forgive me.
実はこれも修行のうちにす
Actually, this is also part of my training.
そんなわけはなくなくなくない
That's not not not not true.
わたしはそうエリート
I am indeed an elite.
(エリート？)
(Elite?)
そうじゃないよエリート
That's not right, an elite.
(どやあ)
(Triumphantly)
エリート巫女？
Elite Miko?
(みこ？)
(Miko?)
エリートアイドル？
Elite idol?
(アイドル？)
(Idol?)
今日もガンガンガンって行きましょう
Let's keep going with all our might today.
ココロ模様曇り色
State of mind, cloudy color.
雨の日も問題 みこパワーで
Even rainy days are no problem with Miko Power.
それアッポたっぺ 笑顔さわやか
[Nonsense words], refreshing smile.
以上うぉやぁ！
That's all, woah!
(チャンネル登録してくれやあり〜！)
(Please subscribe to the channel!)
みこみこみこで ほにゃほにゃうにゃにゃ
Mikomikomiko, hon-nyanya un-nyanya.
さくら くら くら さくらみこ
Sakura, dizzy, dizzy, Sakura Miko.
(みこ！みこ！)
(Miko! Miko!)
みこみこみこで むにゃむにゃぐーぐー
Mikomikomiko, munya-munya goo-goo.
(ぐー！)
(Goo!)
たい焼きめでたい焼き
Taiyaki, auspicious taiyaki.
(ピーマンはNo thank you!)
(Peppers? No thank you!)
みこみこみこで ほにゃほにゃうにゃにゃ
Mikomikomiko, hon-nyanya un-nyanya.
カミサマも ほにゃにゃにゃにゃ…
Even the gods are hon-nyanya-nyanya...
たぶん！
Maybe!
元気の呪文...
The magic word for energy...
みこみこみー！
Miko-miko-mii!
みんな笑顔になあれ！
May everyone be smiling!
わん、つー、あ！
One, two, ah!
間違えたーっ！
I messed up!
にゃっはろー！みんな楽しんでる？
Nyhallo! Everyone having fun?
ここからはスーパーみこみこタイム！
From here on, it's Super Miko-Miko Time!
絶対に遅れずについてきてね？
Make sure you keep up without falling behind!
みんなで一緒にお手を拝借！はい！
Everyone together, let's have your hands! Yes!
みーこ！みーこ！
Miko! Miko!
(みーこ！みーこ！)
(Miko! Miko!)
みこはエリート！
Miko is elite!
(みこはエリート！)
(Miko is elite!)
e-l-i-t-e
(elite!)
みこはエリート イェーイ！
Miko is elite, yeah!
ラストにもう一回踊り切っていくよーっ！
Let's dance through it one more time at the end!
みんな笑顔になあれ！
May everyone be smiling!
わんつーで参拝！みこみこみこ！いぇーい！
Worship on one-two! Miko-miko-miko! Yay!
今日はみこ先輩来てくれてありがとうございました！
Thank you so much for coming today, Miko-senpai!
このマイネームイズエリート、みこ先輩と一緒に歌いたいなって思ってたけど
I wanted to sing 'My Name is Elite' with Miko-senpai, but...
思ったよりも早口で、ラミィはちょっともう、みこ先輩がいかにエリートかが分かりました。ありがとうございました！
It was faster than I thought, and Lamy realized just how elite Miko-senpai is. Thank you!
ラミィちゃん、3周年おめでとう！
Lamy-chan, happy 3rd anniversary!
とってもエリートだったぞ！
You were very elite!
最後にも参拝！みこみこみこ！いぇーい☆
Worship at the end too! Miko-miko-miko! Yay☆
おしまい！
That's it!
うーっ、こんこん！
Uu- konkon!
イェーイ！
Yay!
Say!ファンファーレ！
Say! Fanfare!
うーっ、こんこん！
Uu- konkon!
せーのっ！ Are you ready?
One, two! Are you ready?
お茶ひと息 お茶ですよ
Take a breath, it's tea time
(はい、どうぞ)
(Here you go)
いつもの場所から
From the usual place
元気に手話でご挨拶
Greetings with cheerful sign language
おはこんこんでーすよー！
Oha-konkon!
(始めましょう！)
(Let's begin!)
お喋りにいそしんでゲームと過ごす
Busy chatting and spending time with games
そんな毎日が愛しくて (Fu!)
I love those everyday moments (Fu!)
あれもこれも手を出したくなりガチです
I tend to want to try this and that
歌とかステージは まだまだ恥ずかしいけど
Singing and stages are still embarrassing, but...
支え合って ほら 届けますよ この声も
Supporting each other, look, I'll deliver this voice too
Say! ほら その顔上げて
Say! Look, lift up your face
みんなで手を取れば
If we all take each other's hands
(Fuwa Fuwa Fuwa Fuwa)
Dive! まだまだ道の途中
Dive! Still on the way
世界を越えよう
Let's cross the world
(せーのっ！ Yeah!)
(One, two! Yeah!)
Say! ほら 推しお仕事も
Say! Look, supporting your favorites too
止まらない全力ですから！
It won't stop, because it's full power!
(Fuwa Fuwa Fuwa Fuwa)
夢を書き換えたら
If you rewrite your dreams
追いかけ続けよう
Let's keep chasing them
ともに繋ぐファンファーレ
A fanfare connecting us together
(Dive! Go!) イェーイ！
(Dive! Go!) Yay!
(Hai! Hai!) うーっ、こんこん！
(Hai! Hai!) Uu- konkon!
せーのっ！ Go! Go! Let's Go!
One, two! Go! Go! Let's Go!
ちょっとやらかした時でも
Even when you mess up a bit
(もう大丈夫)
(It's okay now)
気持ち切り替えて
Switch your mood
ぱっとしてる昼下がりには
In the bright afternoon
(昼コンですよ)
(It's afternoon kon)
手をのばして
Reach out your hand
お腹が減ったら すすぐもぐもぐと
When you're hungry, eat right away
お茶の合間 すこんなおやつで (Nya!)
Between tea, with a sukonna snack (Nya!)
黒いあの子には 内緒にして欲しいです
I want you to keep it a secret from that black one
仲間の力と お友達のみなさんと
With the power of friends and all of you comrades
叶えたい思いは 言葉にして ひとつひとつ
Put the feelings you want to fulfill into words, one by one
Say! ほら その手を上げて
Say! Look, raise that hand
みんなで輪になれば
If we all form a circle
(Fuwa Fuwa Fuwa Fuwa)
Dive! まだまだ成長途中
Dive! Still in the middle of growing
問題ないでしょ？ (Fu! Fu!)
No problem, right? (Fu! Fu!)
Say! ほら 明るく元気な
Say! Look, a bright and cheerful...
心が取り柄ですから！
...heart is my strong point!
(Fuwa Fuwa Fuwa Fuwa)
へこみがちな時も
Even when you're feeling down
輝き続けよう
Let's keep shining
ともに繋ぐアンコール
An encore connecting us together
(Dive! Go!) イェーイ！
(Dive! Go!) Yay!
迷い探し手も　響き合って
Even if I get lost searching, we resonate together
ほら世界は　今色めいて
Look, the world is now becoming colorful
Say! さあ、その顔上げて
Say! Come on, look up
みんなで手をとれば
If we all take hands
Dive!
これから夢の先へ
From now on, towards the end of the dream
駆け出そう
Let's start running
Say!
ほら 推しお仕事も
Look, even the job of supporting your 'oshi'
止まらない全力ですから
We're doing it with all our power, it won't stop
大好きな 想いが
My favorite feelings
あふれそうなほど
are about to overflow
ともに繋ぐ ファンファーレ！
Connecting together, fanfare!
Go! Yay!
はい！はい！うーっ、こんこんっ！
Hi! Hi! Uu, Konkon!
ふーっ！こんこんっ！
Fuu! Konkon!
はい！はい！ふーっ！
Hi! Hi! Fuu!
ふわふわふわふわ！ いぇーい！
Fuwa fuwa fuwa fuwa! Yay!
はい！はい！うーっ、こんこんっ！
Hi! Hi! Uu, Konkon!
はい！はい！はい！
Hi! Hi! Hi!
ワン ツー スリー フォー！ いぇーーい！
One Two Three Four! Yaaaay!
フブキ先輩ありがとうございました！
Fubuki-senpai, thank you very much!
あたしジャンクフードな思考回路
My thought process is like junk food
咽せる退廃的な異常行動
Choking on decadent, abnormal behavior
もどしたい！ もどしたい！
Want to go back! Want to go back!
もどしたい！
Want to go back!
不毛地帯なら
If it's a wasteland...
人生リセットボタンぽちーw
Life Reset Button, click-w
人生リセットの断末魔
The death throes of a life reset
人生にネット冗談きつーw
Internet jokes about life are harsh-w
人生リセットボタンぽちーw
Life Reset Button, click-w
人生リセットボタンぽち
Life Reset Button, click
あたしジャンクフードな思考回路
My thought process is like junk food
咽せる退廃的な異常行動
Choking on decadent, abnormal behavior
もどしたい！ もどしたい！
Want to go back! Want to go back!
もどしたい！
Want to go back!
不毛地帯なら
If it's a wasteland...
人生リセットボタンぽちーw
Life Reset Button, click-w
人生リセットの断末魔
The death throes of a life reset
人生にネット冗談きつーw
Internet jokes about life are harsh-w
人生リセットボタンぽちーw
Life Reset Button, click-w
人生リセットボタンぽち
Life Reset Button, click
あたしジャンクフードな思考回路
My thought process is like junk food
咽せる退廃的な異常行動
Choking on decadent, abnormal behavior
もどしたい！ もどしたい！
Want to go back! Want to go back!
もどしたい！
Want to go back!
不毛地帯なら
If it's a wasteland...
人生リセットボタンぽちーw
Life Reset Button, click-w
人生リセットの断末魔
The death throes of a life reset
人生にネット冗談きつーw
Internet jokes about life are harsh-w
人生リセットボタンぽちーw
Life Reset Button, click-w
人生リセットボタンぽち
Life Reset Button, click
魅惑を詰め運ぼ
Let's pack and carry the fascination
秘宝はここにある
The treasure is right here
危なげな デンジャラス マリンスメル
Risky, dangerous Marine Smell
これ開けたら君たちに 何してあげるべきかな？
If I open this, what should I do for you guys?
探してたのは Love me?
What you were looking for was, 'Love me?'
あ、そんなに引っ付いて 駄目だぞ？かなぁ？
Ah, you can't stick to me like that, okay? Maybe?
お宝よりも魅惑的なモノ 見つけちゃった？
Did you find something more fascinating than treasure?
いいじゃない
That's good, isn't it?
砂糖がね、とろけた
Sugar, you know, has melted
極上の海賊の秘宝
The finest pirate treasure
それは私
That's me
熱に触れ漂う
Floating, touched by the fever
香りをそう 怖がらないで
Don't be so afraid of the scent
あけてみて
Open it up
Sexy 世界一
Sexy number one in the world
Super ピチピチ
Super fresh
ぶっちゃけ船長 捕まえたくない？
To be honest, don't you want to catch the Captain?
You're gonna get the treasure
Maybe tasty me
私の甘さが欲しいでしょ
You want my sweetness, right?
秘宝の鍵を
The key to the treasure
優しく挿して
Insert it gently
宝庫の扉
The door to the treasury
マジで早く開けて
Seriously, open it quickly
じれったい あなたの手
Your hands are so teasing
返さずにこぼす 甘い吐息のティー
Spilling sweet sighs of tea without returning them
旬な薔薇が
A seasonal rose...
I'm Your Treasure Box
～ あなたは マリンせんちょうを たからばこからみつけた ～
~ You found Captain Marine from the treasure box ~
We will sail the ocean!
鳴らそうぜ　大海原
Let's sound the call across the great ocean
Summer sun smiling with glee!
お宝に　駆け進め
Race towards the treasure
Sailing over the ocean wave!
混ざるワールドカラー　何探してんの？
Mixed world colors, what are you looking for?
Now please grab my galaxy!
Open, open this box!
Open, it's right now! Oh, oh, always!
さあ、もう待てない！
Now, I can't wait any longer!
開けろー！
Open it!
泣く子も黙る　Naughtyなお色気ビーム
A naughty sexy beam that will even make a crying child silent
君たちも　もう我慢できなくない？
Aren't you guys unable to hold back anymore either?
You're gonna own the pleasure. Maybe love of me?
私の全てを　手に入れて
Take all of me
金銀財宝！
Gold, silver, and treasures!
はした金でしょ
It's just pocket change, right?
シワシワになっちゃう！
You're gonna get all wrinkled up!
誰か助けて！
Someone help me!
マジで遠慮しすぎ
Seriously, you're being too reserved
君たち　何考えてんの？
What are you guys thinking?
分かってる　脱がす覚悟
I know, you're ready to undress me
だから今すぐ　開けてよ
So open it right now
宝箱
Treasure Box
あなたの　I'm Your Treasure Box
Your... I'm your treasure box
君、君たち、開けて！
You, you guys, open it!
夢花火
歌：雪花ラミィ / 百鬼あやめ
Dream Fireworks
Vocals: Yukihana Lamy / Nakiri Ayame
鈴の音響く
The sound of bells echoing
深い夜とお月さま
In the deep night and the moon
今宵宴の　宵を
Tonight's banquet... the evening...
高鳴り堪え
Suppressing the throbbing heart
ああ　式神連れ立って
Ah, accompanied by shikigami
戯れに興じるの
Amusing ourselves in play
流れ行く時を想う
Thinking of the flowing time
消えゆく意味ならば
If it's the meaning of fading away
この刹那さえ　美しくよ
Then even this moment is beautiful
咲かせて　空高く
Let it bloom, high in the sky
そっとはんなり　はんなり夢花火
Softly, elegantly, elegantly, dream fireworks
ふんわりふんわり　願うのは
Softly, softly, what I wish for
現世の　思い出だけ
Is only the memories of this fleeting world
ずっと幾年　時を重ねて
Accumulating time over many years
巡り会う世は情け
The world where we meet again is filled with kindness
常しえに余韻　歌って笑っていたいのだ
Wishing to sing and laugh in the eternal afterglow
静けさ満ちる
Silence fills the air
浮かぶ三つ影法師
Three silhouettes floating
今宵祭りの　後よ
Tonight, after the festival
寂しささえ
Even the loneliness
ああ　皆共々想いながら
Ah, while thinking of everyone
微睡みへ委ねるの
Yielding to the slumber
生まれては弾け消える
Born, bursting, and disappearing
泡沫の調べは
The melody of the bubbles
その一瞬も　大切に今
Treasuring even that one instant
光らせて　鮮やかに
Make it shine brilliantly
そっときんなり　きんなり夢花火
Softly, goldenly, goldenly, dream fireworks
ひっそりひっそり　祈るのは
Quietly, quietly, what I pray for
永遠の　楽しさだけ
Is only eternal joy
ずっと幾年　時を重ねて
Accumulating time over many years
思い出だす世はあわれ
The world I remember is deeply moving
心ゆくまで　踊って騒いでいたいのだ
Wishing to dance and make merry to my heart's content
宿る気持ちならば この儚さも 彩りとなれ
If it's a lingering feeling, let even this fleetingness become a hue.
咲かせて 鮮やかに
Let it bloom vividly
見届けて
Witness it
そっとはんなり はんなり 夢花火
Gently, elegantly, elegantly, dream fireworks
ふんわり ふんわり 祈るのは
Softly, softly, what I pray for is
現世の 楽しさだけ
Only the joys of this transient world
いつまでも 幾年 時を重ねて
Forever, through many years, overlapping time
巡り会う 世は情け
The world where we meet again is full of compassion
忘れないように
So as not to forget
とこしえに私は 皆と笑っていたいのだ
Forever, I want to be laughing with everyone
影ひとつ 止まってく音は たなびかせず
A single shadow, the sound that stops without trailing away
流れ出す 朝焼けの空を 通りゆく
Flowing out, passing through the sunrise sky
聞こえた 震えてる声の 意味は誰だろう
I heard it, whose meaning is in that trembling voice?
何でかな 会いたくなったんだ 会えるかな
I wonder why I wanted to see you, will I see you?
夢ひとつ 鞄のポケット 忍ばせず
A single dream, not hiding it in the bag's pocket
風ひとつ 始まりの朝に ドキドキ
A single breeze, heart pounding on the morning of a beginning
思い出す 結んだ指に 残った温度は
I remember, the temperature remaining in our linked fingers
今もまだ 青く残ってる 褪せぬまま
Is still blue even now, without fading
とりあえず 嘘じゃないかな 飛んでくのも無理だね
For now, it's not a lie, is it? It's impossible to fly, too
それだったら 歩き出してみよう
If that's the case, let's try walking out
そうやって 描いた今日を 通り越して
That way, passing through the today we drew
明日はもっと 君のそばへ前へ
Tomorrow, further to your side, forward
そう前へ 少しずつ 進んでいく
Yes, forward, moving little by little
一歩 五十歩 百歩 踏み出して
Taking one step, fifty steps, a hundred steps
揺らめいてる 君が 青く滲む 綺麗に
Swaying, you blur into blue, beautifully
会いに行く 会いに行こう 今すぐ
I'm going to see you, let's go see you right now
凪ひとつ さざめく音に 耳を立てて
A single lull, pricking my ears to the murmuring sound
赤く青く 夕映えの空の ほうき星
Red and blue, a comet in the evening sky
不思議と 不安な時も 怖くないから
Strangely, even when I'm anxious, I'm not afraid
手を振って 俯かないように 歩いてこう
Waving my hand, let's walk so as not to look down
憧れても 願っていても 誰にもなれないな
Even if I long for it, even if I wish for it, I can't become anyone else
それだったら 自分になってみよう
In that case, let's try being myself
そうやって 目指した今日を 飛び越えて
That way, jumping over the today we aimed for
明日はきっと 会えるから じゃあね
Tomorrow for sure, we'll see each other, so goodbye
そしたらね 一緒に 何を話そう
And then, what shall we talk about together?
一歩 五十歩 百歩 重ね合って
One step, fifty steps, a hundred steps, overlapping
紡いでいく 時間が 溶けていく
The time we spin is melting away
それでもいつかは 夢が終わるなら
Still, if one day the dream ends
それでも良いかな 君がいるんなら
Even then it might be okay, if you are here
世界の中で 出会えた君が
In this world, you whom I met
理由になったら それでも良いかな
If you become the reason, even then it might be okay
一人の今日を 飛び越えて
Jumping over this solitary today
描いた今日を 通り越して
Passing through the today we drew
明日はもっと 君のそばへ前へ
Tomorrow, further to your side, forward
そう前へ 少しずつ 進むよ
Yes, forward, I'll move little by little
一歩 五十歩 百歩 千歩 繰り返して
Repeating one step, fifty, a hundred, a thousand steps
指に触れる 君が 青く滲む 綺麗に
You, touching my fingers, blur into blue, beautifully
いつまでも そばにいて 良いかな
Is it okay to be by your side forever?
コンタウズ ハーレイディア オン シャルル・イース
Contawz harley dia on Charles-is
アニ ミィタ ポ ヴォティ マイ ジ ュリィク
Ani miita po voti mai juriiku
ズィ クロゥス オクノ クレズ アイナゥ ケィティーン
Zii kuroosu okuno kurezu ainau keitiin
ハプ アム ユ キル シャル ベ イル
Hapu amu yu kiru sharu be iru
ヤイ ピィリ ダレ オ ミィラ サ ク チョ
Yai piiri dare o miira sa ku cho
フィギナ ヴェ ミィナ フリ ダ フィ ア
Figina ve miira furi da fi a
ディセ フィ ラ セナ ヴェ ティ カ ス
Dise fi ra sena ve ti ka su
テム ヴォ ォィ ラジュ モ ロフ ハ ハプ ア
Temu vo oi raju mo rofu ha hapu a
コンターズ ハレリィア オン シャルイィース
Kontazu hareriia on Shaluiys
アニ ミィタ ポ ヴォティ マイ ジ ュリィク
Ani miita po voti mai juriiku
アイ ノ ヴェ ア トロム ストゥリィア
Ai no ve a toromu suturiia
ノン トゥ キァス トゥ ォリィア
Non tu kiasu tu oriia
コンターズ ハレリィア オン シャルイィース
Kontazu hareriia on Shaluiys
アニ ミィタ ポ ヴォティ マイ ジ ュリィク
Ani miita po voti mai juriiku
ズィ クロゥス オクノ クレズ アイナゥ ケィティーン
Zii kuroosu okuno kurezu ainau keitiin
ハプ アム ユ キル シャル ベ イル
Hapu amu yu kiru sharu be iru
ヴェス トゥガ リガ リ ピィリ ア
Vesu tuga riga ri piiri a
バラ コン サル ミィア リ ラ ヴォ
Bara kon saru miia ri ra vo
クルス ヴェニィ ア ニィナ イ ヂュリィク
Kurusu venii a niira i juriiku
メネ ラ ス テム ヴォ クルル
Mene ra su temu vo kururu
ディリ ラロ ピィ プロ ノ テムル
Diri raro pi puro no temuru
パル マイ ビィレ マ ム セリ フィ
Paru mai biire ma mu seri fi
オモ パ パ ヴァ ミ ノ プンダ ル ネ
Omo pa pa va mi no punda ru ne
ヴェナ ヴェ ア サ ラ メ
Vena ve a sa ra me
デ カン トゥ ミ ラ リ ラ
De kan tu mi ra ri ra
ハプ フィ ラ セ ミィ ア
Hapu fi ra se mii a
フィ モ ラ セロ メ クォニィ ア
Fi mo ra sero me kwonii a
ティミ ヴォォイ プロ ポ ネ オ ダ
Timi vooi puro po ne o da
フィ モ ラ セロ ラ ラ
Fi mo ra sero ra ra
コンターズ ハレリィア オン シャルイィース
Kontazu hareriia on Shaluiys
アニ ミィタ ポ ヴォティ マイ ジ ュリィク
Ani miita po voti mai juriiku
ズィ クロゥス オクノ クレズ アイナゥ ケィティーン
Zii kuroosu okuno kurezu ainau keitiin
ハプ アム ユ キル シャル ベ イル
Hapu amu yu kiru sharu be iru
モ リュ ペ サム ト
Mo ryu pe samu to
モ ラ テ カン ト
Mo ra te kan to
テム ヴォ ォィ ラジュ モ ロフ ホー
Temu vo oi raju mo rofu hoo
テム ヴォ ォィ ラジュ モ ロフ ハ ハプ ア
Temu vo oi raju mo rofu ha hapu a
わー！
Wow!
ということで、怒涛のゲストパートいかがだったでしょうか？
And with that, how was the intense guest segment?
えー、おかゆ先輩、かなたん、みこ先輩、フブキ先輩、
Um, Okayu-senpai, Kanatan, Miko-senpai, Fubuki-senpai,
ちょこ先輩、また、マリン先輩、あやめ先輩、
Choco-senpai, as well as Marine-senpai, Ayame-senpai,
あくあ先輩、アキロゼ先輩、ありがとう！
Aqua-senpai, Aki Rosenthal-senpai, thank you so much!
ということでね、雪民さんはどうだった？
So then, Yukimin, how was it?
良かったと思う？
Do you think it was good?
うん、うん。
Yeah, yeah.
どう？ラミィちゃんしか愛せない？
What do you think? Do you only have eyes for Lamy-chan?
うん、うん。
Yeah, yeah.
あー、雪民さん好き！むー！
Ah, I love you Yukimin! Mwah!
んま、んま、んま...
Mma, mma, mma...
な、何、真顔？
Wh-What's with the blank stare?
真顔かよ雪民さん。
Are you giving me a blank stare, Yukimin-san?
ラミィのこんな熱い抱擁、ラブキスが...
Lamy's passionate embrace and love kisses are...
んまんまんま...
Mma, mma, mma...
ということでね、
So, putting...
茶番はこれぐらいにして。
...the skit aside for now.
さりげなく衣装チェンジもいたしました！
I've also subtly changed my outfit!
みんなホロライブサマーとかね、
I'm sure everyone has seen
雪民さんも見てると思うけど。
Hololive Summer and all, but...
まさかね、ラミィの雪民さん、
Surely, Lamy's Yukimin-san...
この水着姿見慣れてなんかないよね？
...haven't gotten used to seeing this swimsuit yet, right?
いないよね？もっと見たいでしょ？
No, right? You want to see more, don't you?
いいんだよ見ても。
It's okay to look.
いいんだよほら。
It's okay, see?
いいんだよ、雪民さん、ほら。
It's okay, Yukimin-san, see?
こんな、こんな、
You can see me from this, this...
こんな間近で雪民さん見れるんだよ、
...this close, Yukimin-san!
良かったね！
Lucky you!
ということでね、ここからは
So, from here we're returning
ラミィのソロパートに戻りますので。
to Lamy's solo part.
雪民さんはあっちで応援しててくださーい！
Yukimin-san, please cheer me on from over there!
それではみなさん聴いてください。
Well then, everyone, please listen to:
かくしん的☆めたまるふぉ～ぜっ！
Kakushinteki☆Metamaruphose!
U・M・R！
U-M-R!
UMAじゃないよ　う・ま・る！
Not a UMA, but U-MA-RU!
いつだって全身全霊　遊び倒せ！
Always give it your all and play to your heart's content!
もっと　もっと　楽しめよ乙女
More, more, enjoy yourself, young maiden
みんなに気付かれないように
So that nobody notices
いざゆけ　干物妹ライフ
Let's go, Himouto life!
お気に入りのフードかぶり
Putting on my favorite hood
今日も今日とてゴロゴロして
Lounging around again today
大好物のポテチを手に
With my favorite potato chips in hand
パソコンとにらめっこしよう
Let's have a staring contest with the PC
立てば芍薬座れば牡丹
Standing like a peony, sitting like a tree peony
歩く姿は百合の花
Walking like a lily
誰もが羨む完璧JK
The perfect high school girl everyone envies
ほら玄関くぐったら変身だ
Look, once I'm through the front door, it's transformation time
さあグータラしよう
Now, let's be lazy
いつだって『食う！寝る！遊ぶ！』の3連コンボ
Always the 3-hit combo of "Eat! Sleep! Play!"
ずっと　ずっと　ゲームは友達
Forever and ever, games are my friends
お兄ちゃんは厳しいけど
Big brother is strict
きっと　きっと　許してくれちゃうの
But I'm sure, I'm sure he'll forgive me
ワガママ放題は大好きの裏返し
Being selfish is just my way of saying I love you
U・M・R！
U-M-R!
UMAじゃないよ　う・ま・る！
Not a UMA, but U-MA-RU!
外では猫をかぶり
Putting on a polite act outside
今日も明日も演じるのです
I'll play the part today and tomorrow too
大好評の笑顔を武器に
With my popular smile as a weapon
トモダチにバレないように
So my friends won't find out
立てば2頭身座ればまんまる
Standing at two heads tall, sitting like a ball
歩く姿はちんちくりん
Walking like a shrimp
誰でも癒せる愛嬌マスコット！？
An adorable mascot who can heal anyone!?
さあ限界超えるまでパーティナイト
Now, it's party night until we hit the limit
宴の始まりだー！
The banquet has begun!
みんなのおかげで、雪花ラミィ3周年を迎えることができました！
Thanks to everyone, I was able to reach my 3rd anniversary!
4年目もたくさんたくさん頑張っていくので、
I'll keep working hard in my 4th year too,
よろしくお願いしますー！
so please keep supporting me!
可憐で優雅な女の子演じてみても
Even if I play the part of a lovely and elegant girl
お兄ちゃんだけは騙せない
I can't fool only you, big brother
嫌われたくないもん
Because I don't want you to hate me.
素直に言えない『ありがとう』
I can't honestly say "thank you"
態度で示そう
So I'll show it through my actions
だぁー！前言撤回！
Dah! I take it back!
あぁもうイイじゃん！
Oh, whatever!
お兄ちゃん何て知らないいっ！！
I don't care about big brother at all!!
なんつって！一心同体2人でひとつ
Just kidding! We're two hearts as one
だって　だって　それが兄弟でしょ？
Because, because, that's what being siblings is, right?
一蓮托生2人きりの運命共同体
Sharing the same fate, just the two of us, a community of destiny
今日だって自由奔放　笑い飛ばせ！
Even today, being free-spirited, laugh it off!
もっと　もっと　楽しんだモン勝ち
More, more, the one who enjoys it most wins
天真爛漫スマイルで
With a naive and innocent smile
ぎゅっと　ぎゅっと　心を掴んじゃうの
I'll tightly, tightly grab your heart
やりたい放題は信頼の裏返し
Doing whatever I want is just my way of saying I trust you
U・M・R！
U-M-R!
UMAじゃないよ　う・ま・る！
Not a UMA, but U-MA-RU!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
はい、おしまい！
That's all!
はい！ということで皆さん、
Yes! So everyone,
聴いていただきました、かくしん的☆めたまるふぉ～ぜっ！
you just heard: Kakushinteki☆Metamaruphose!
イェーイ！
Yay!
えー、この後の流れはみんな
Uh, you all know the flow
恒例だから分かるよね？
after this, right?
そう！
That's right!
ラミィのオリ曲！新曲！
Lamy's original song! A new song!
歌いまーす！
I'm going to sing!
イェーーーイ！
Yaaaaaay!
ということでね
So,
皆さん、聴いてください！
everyone, please listen!
Lamy＊Love♡Fest☆
由々しき事態の絵面
A scene of a grave situation
(わー！)
(Whoa!)
気付けば溢れるラブみ
Overflowing Lamy-love before I knew it
(Love me!)
恥じらい捨てるが正解
Discarding shyness is the right answer
(Ding-dong!)
なげきすまっちゅはご愛嬌
The air kiss is a little charm
こんらみですー！
Kon-Lamy!
お酒と雪民さんを
I'm Yukihana Lamy,
こよなく愛する5期生
a 5th gen member who dearly loves
顔が肝臓 雪花ラミィです！
alcohol and Yukimin, with a liver for a face!
朝昼晩と色んな時間に
I stream at various times of the day,
配信してるので
morning, noon, and night,
お好きな時間に
so come and see me
会いに来てね！
whenever you like!
あーもう全然間に合わない！！！
Ah, I can't keep up at all!!!
(ケッケッラッカ！)
(Kek-kek-rakka!)
雪の国から
From the land of snow,
(ケッケッラッカ！)
(Kek-kek-rakka!)
やってきました！
I have arrived!
勘違いされてますが
Though people often mistake me,
雪女じゃないんです！
I'm not a Yuki-onna!
冬は苦手なんです...
I'm actually not good with winter...
さてさてここいらで
Now then, around here,
とりあえず一杯
let's have a drink for now,
少々お待ち！
just a moment!
(おかわりー！)
(Refill!)
パッパラッパ酔いはじめ
Pa-pa-ra-pa, getting tipsy,
皆さんもご一緒に！
everyone join in!
(いぇす！)
(Yes!)
今宵酔いどれで
Tonight, let's get drunk,
さあ！飲み明かそう！
come on! Let's drink all night!
(ちぇあ！)
(Cheers!)
ラミィの世界へ おいでませ
Welcome to Lamy's world
ここは天国かユートピア
Is this heaven or Utopia?
(とびゃー！)
(To-pya!)
アッチに行って
Go over there,
コッチに行って
come over here,
あばばばばば
Abababababa
大きい夢叶えましょう
Let's make big dreams come true
ばんざい！からの
Banzai! And then
まる！からのバツ！
Circle! And then X!
ここはひょうきんなシャングリラ☆
This is a funny Shangri-La☆
ツッコミだって大喜利だって
Tsukkomi or Oogiri,
お手の物
it's all a breeze
世界中幸せを届けます
Delivering happiness all over the world
雪花ラミィ！
Yukihana Lamy!
(満面笑顔でいかかとおね！)
(With a big smile!)
こんな声だってどうだい
How about a voice like this?
耳の奥響くの脳内
Resonating deep within your ears
そろそろやめていいかい...？
Can I stop soon...?
(ダメ！)
(No!)
ココでもう一度 やめなさい！
Once more here, stop it!
(うわ...)
(Ugh...)
(テッテッレット！)
(Te-te-ret-to!)
黒歴史なら
If it's a dark history,
(テッテッレット！)
(Te-te-ret-to!)
忘れちゃって！
just forget it!
もうラミィのライフはゼロなんだよ！
Lamy's life is already at zero!
これ以上やめなー、やめろー、
No more of this, stop it, stop it,
やめなさい！！
Stop it!!
おーっと酔いが回ってきた
Whoops, the tipsiness is setting in
抜き足差し足忍び足
Walking on tiptoe, stealthily
千鳥足
Tottering with a drunk step
ぐるぐる回る世界
A world spinning round and round
絡まるぺろぺろぴー
Tangled tongue, slurred words
らりるれろれらりら
Ra-ri-ru-re-ro-re-ra-ri-ra
あれ？なんか舌が回らないんらけろ...？
Huh? My tongue won't move properly...?
ふぅ...
Phew...
咲いて乱れて雪月花
Bloom and scatter, Setsu-getsu-ka
ここは天国かユートピア
Is this heaven or Utopia?
ニッチもサッチもいかなくて
Finding myself in a tight spot,
あばばばば
Ababababa
世界、未来語りましょう
Let's talk about the world and future
飲んで飲まれて雪夜月
Drink and be drunk, Yukiyozuki
ここは絢爛なアルカディア
This is a gorgeous Arcadia
(てぃーだー！)
(Ti-da!)
花鳥だって風月だって叶わない
Kacho-Fugetsu doesn't compare
世界中ラミィ色に染め上げよう！
Let's dye the whole world in Lamy's color!
ほらほら！
Come on, come on!
まだまだ！
Not yet, not yet!
ここからいくよー！？
Here we go!?
せーのっ！ギターカモーン！！！
One, two! Guitar, come on!!!
推してくれたから
Because you supported me,
頑張ってこれました！
I could work hard to get here!
ホント、ありがとうね！
Really, thank you so much!
今度はラミィが背中押してあげるから
This time, Lamy will give you a push,
ずっとずっとそばにいてね♪
so stay by my side forever♪
泣きたい時こそ Lamy＊Love♡Fest☆
When you want to cry, Lamy＊Love♡Fest☆
ラミィの世界は終わらない
Lamy's world will never end
ここは天国かユートピア
Is this heaven or Utopia?
(とびゃー！)
(To-pya!)
明日だって明後日だって Happy Happy Days
Tomorrow and the day after, Happy Happy Days
この先、10年、100年もしあわせでしょ！
We'll be happy for the next 10, 100 years!
(それー！)
(There it is!)
ばんざい！からの
Banzai! And then
まる！からのまる！
Circle! And then circle!
ここは最高なシャングリラ☆
This is the best Shangri-La☆
大雨だって嵐だって
Heavy rain or storm,
虹になれ
become a rainbow
世界中明日元気になーれ！
May everyone in the world be energetic tomorrow!
(満面笑顔で Lamy＊Love♡Fest☆)
(With a big smile, Lamy＊Love♡Fest☆)
みんな大好きですっ！
I love you all!
今日も今日とて元気にお届けしまーす♪
Today as always, I'm delivering energy to you♪
ルームウェアの抱き枕カバーは、リン☆ユウママに描き下ろしてもらいました。
The room wear body pillow cover was drawn by Rin Yuu-mama.
裏と表でガラッと雰囲気が変わるけど、雪民さんはどっちが好きかな？
The atmosphere changes completely between the front and back, but which one do Yukimin like?
そして、むーらん先生にイラストを書いていただきました、ラミィとお揃いマグカップ。
And, the matching mug with Lamy, illustrated by Mulan-sensei.
持ち手がハートになっていて、すっごく可愛いでしょ？
The handle is shaped like a heart, isn't it super cute?
「大好きな君専用」っていうのは、
"Exclusively for the one I love"...
ラミィが君に使ってほしくて書いたんだからね！
...is because I wrote it wanting you to use it!
そしてラミィとお揃い雪民スリッパ！
And then, matching Yukimin slippers with Lamy!
ラミィが履いてるのはだいふくのスリッパだけど、
Lamy is wearing Daifuku slippers, but...
雪民さんは雪民さん専用のスリッパ。
...Yukimin-san has their own exclusive slippers.
お揃いで仲良く歩こうね！
Let's walk together as a matching pair!
そして記念ボイスはシチュエーションボイス...
And the anniversary voice is a situation voice...
「同棲彼女の甘々おやすみボイス」となっております！
..."Cohabitation Girlfriend's Sweet Goodnight Voice"!
ラミィの抱き枕をぎゅーっと抱きながら聴いてね！
Listen to it while hugging Lamy's dakimakura tight!
そして活動3周年記念フルセットはこちら！
And here is the 3rd Anniversary Full Set!
特典ボイスは「同棲彼女の甘々お目覚めボイス」となっています。
The bonus voice is "Cohabitation Girlfriend's Sweet Wake-up Voice."
記念ボイスの続きのお話になってるので、こっちもぜひぜひ聴いてね！
It's a continuation of the anniversary voice story, so please listen to this one too!
そしてチェキ風ブロマイドカードは、
And the cheki-style bromide card...
雪民さんに寝てる間に隠し撮りされちゃった...なラミィの1枚。
...is a photo of Lamy caught sleeping by a Yukimin-san.
ちょっと恥ずかしいけど、飾ってくれると嬉しいな。
It's a bit embarrassing, but I'd be happy if you displayed it.
それでは、みんなここまで見てくれて本当にありがとう！
Well then, everyone, thank you so much for watching until the end!
みんなが推してくれたから、雪花ラミィは3周年を迎えることができました。
Because you all supported me, Yukihana Lamy was able to reach her 3rd anniversary.
これからもたくさんたくさん頑張っていくので、みんな応援よろしくね！
I'll keep working very, very hard from now on, so everyone, please keep supporting me!
雪民さん、大好き！ラブ、んーまっ、ちゅ！
Yukimin-san, I love you! Love, *mwah*!